Guide to the Picture File, 1600s-1979 and undated, bulk 1814-1950
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library Duke University Durham, N.C., USA
- People Series, 1700s, 1714-1974, 1900s and undated, (22 boxes)
  - A-H, 1700s, 1714-1974, 1900s and undated
    - Doak, William Nuckles, circa 1930s, (black-and-white photograph) (Folder M820)
    - Dobbin, James Cochrane, 1800s, (engraving) (Folder M821)
    - Doles, George, 1800s, (engraving) (Folder M822)
    - Dormer, Robert, Earl of Caernarvon, 1833 Apr. 1, (engraving) (Folder M823)
    - Doub, Landon L., undated, (black-and-white photograph) (Folder M824)
    - Doub, Peter, undated, (lithograph)
    - Doub, William Blake, 1800s, (black-and-white photograph) (Folder M825)
      Photograph of a daguerrotype.
    - Doub, William Clark, circa 1870, (card photograph) (Folder M826)
    - Douglas, Stephen A., 1862, (engraving) (Folder M827)
    - Dowd, William Bruce, 1880, (card photograph) (Folder M828)
    - Dowell, G. J., 1800s, (card photograph) (Folder M829)
    - Doyle, Sir Charles William, 1829, (engraving) (Folder M830)
      Includes signature.
    - Drake, Sir Francis, 1829 Apr. 1 and undated, (2 engravings) (Folder M831)
    - Drayton, William Henry, 1872, (engraving) (Folder M832)
    - Dreiser, Theodore, undated, (black-and-white photographic illustration) (Folder M833)
    - Dryden, John (1631-1700), 1800s, (engraving) (Folder M834)
    - DuBose, D. M., 1800s, (engraving) (Folder M835)
    - Dudley, Lady Jane (Grey), 1825 Sept. 1, (engraving) (Folder M836)
    - Dudley, Robert, Earl of Leicester, undated, (engraving) (Folder M837)
    - Duignan, William H., circa 1840, (black-and-white photograph) (Folder M838)
      From the George Jacob Holyoake Papers.
    - Duke, Brodie Leonidas, undated, (1 black-and-white photograph and 1 engraving) (Folder M839)
    - Duke, Brodie Leonidas, et al, circa 1912, (black-and-white photograph) (Folder M840)
    - Duke Family Pictures, undated, (6 card photographs) (Folder M841)
      Received from "Four Acres." These unidentified images left in Picture File; 13 others removed to James B. Duke and Benjamin N. Duke Papers.
    - Duke, Washington, undated, (engraving) (Folder M842)
    - Duke, Zebbean (Mrs.), 1900s, (black-and-white photograph) (Folder M843)
    - Duncan, Adam, Viscount Duncan, 1831 and 1800s, (2 engravings) (Folder M844)
    - Dundas, Henry, First Viscount Melville, 1831, (engraving)
      Removed to Oversize Subseries, Box M03, Folder OV72.
    - Dundas, Robert Saunders, Second Viscount Melville, 1840, (engraving) (Folder M845)
    - Dupont, Samuel Francis, 1800s, (1 engraving and 1 card photograph) (Folder M846)
      One engraving removed to Box M03, Folder OV73 in the Oversize Subseries.
    - Duranty, Walter, 1900s, (black-and-white photograph) (Folder M847)
    - Durell, Edward Henry, undated, (engraving) (Folder M848)
    - Durham, Bartlett, 1800s, (card photograph) (Folder M849)
      From the Wm. K. Boyd Mss.
    - Dyer, George Leland, 1909 Jan. 1, (card photograph)
      Removed to Box M03, Folder OV74, Oversize Subseries.
      Signed by Dyer with dedication to friend.
    - Early, Jubal Anderson, 1800s, (black-and-white photograph, engraving) (Folder M850)
      Photograph is of an engraving.
      One engraving was removed to Box M03, Folder OV75 in the Oversize Subseries.
    - Eberhart, Richard, 1961, (black-and-white photograph) (Folder M851)
    - Echols, Joseph, 1800s, (card photograph) (Folder M852)
    - Echols, W. H., Sr., 1800s, (card photograph) (Folder M853)
      From the Albert Aylor Manuscripts.
    - Edward VI, King of England, 1833 Sept. 1, (engraving)
      Removed to Oversize Subseries, Box M03, Folder OV76.
    - Edward VII as Prince of Wales, with wife and child, undated, (card photograph) (Folder M854)
    - Egerton, Francis, Third and Last Duke of Bridgewater, 1833, (engraving) (Folder M855)
    - Einstein, Albert, 1935, (3 black-and-white photographs) (Folder M856)
      Negative available. Two of these photographs are duplicates.
    - Einstein, Albert, 1900s, (clipping)
      Removed to Folder OV77, Box LG03, Oversize Subseries.
    - Eisenhower, Dwight David, circa 1940s, (black-and-white photograph) (Folder M857)
    - Elbert, Samuel, 1798, (black-and-white photograph) (Folder M858)
      Photograph of an engraving. Includes explanatory letters from the Naval Historical Foundation.
    - Elena, Queen of Italy, undated, (postcard) (Folder M859)
    - Elizabeth, Princess of Great Britain and Landgravine..., undated, (engraving) (Folder M860)
    - Elizabeth I, Queen of England and Ireland, undated, (engraving) (Folder M861)
    - Ellicott, Benjamin, 1822, (black-and-white photograph) (Folder M862)
      Photograph of an oil painting.
    - Ellicott, Joseph, circa 1820, (black-and-white photograph) (Folder M863)
      Photograph of a deguerrotype copy of an oil painting.
    - Elliott, Stephen, (1806-1866), 1800s, (2 engravings) (Folder M864)
      One engraving is from the Geo. Hist. Society.
    - [Ellis, Charles and Margaret Keeling (Nimmo)], circa 1870 and 1800s, (2 card photographs) (Folder M865)
    - Ellis, George James Welbore Agar, First Baron Dover, 1830, (engraving) (Folder M866)
    - Ellis, Henry Welbore Agar, Viscount Clifden, 1830 and 1836, (2 engravings) (Folder M867)
    - Ellis, Richard S., Jr., 1800s, (card photograph) (Folder M868)
    - Ellis, Thomas H., 1879 Mar. 17, (card photograph) (Folder M869)
    - Ellsworth, Elmer Ephraim, 1862, (engraving) (Folder M870)
      Attached note: "This happened in Alexandria at the Marshall House."
    - Ellsworth, Oliver, 1800s, (engraving) (Folder M871)
    - Elzey, Arnold, 1864 June 18, (black-and-white photograph) (Folder M872)
    - Emerson, Ralph Waldo, 1860, 1873, and 1800s, (3 card photographs) (Folder M873)
    - Emerson, Ralph Waldo, 1800s, (2 engravings) (Folder M874)
    - Emerson, Ralph Waldo, 1800s, (black-and-white photographic illustration) (Folder M875)
      Removed to Oversize Subseries, Box M03, Folder OV78.
    - Emmet, Thomas Addis, 1800s, (engraving) (Folder M876)
    - Emory, John, 1820, (engraving) (Folder M877)
    - Engelmann, Gerson S., 1900s, (black-and-white photograph) (Folder M878)
    - De l'Épée, Charles Michel, Abbé, 1800s, (engraving) (Folder M879)
    - Erasmus, Desiderius, 1800s, (engraving) (Folder M880)
    - Ernest Augustus, Duke of Cumberland and King of Hanover, 1832, (engraving) (Folder M881)
    - Erskine, Thomas, First Baron Erskine (1750-1823), undated, (engraving) (Folder M882)
    - Estaing, Charles Hector, Comte D', undated, (3 engravings and 1 lithograph) (Folder M883)
    - Everett, Edward, undated, (2 engravings) (Folder M884)
      Larger image from Georgia Hist. Society.
    - Everett, Reuben Oscar, undated, (black-and-white photograph) (Folder M885)
    - Ewell, Richard S., undated, (1 engraving and 1 card photograph) (Folder M886)
    - Excell, Edwin Othello, 1887, (card photograph) (Folder M887)
    - Faries, Thomas A., 1886 and 1800s, (5 card photographs) (Folder M888)
    - Farragut, David Glasgow, 1863, 1865 and 1800s, (2 card photograph and 6 engravings) (Folder M889)
      Larger engraving may have genuine autograph.
    - Father Divine, undated, (black-and-white photographic illustration) (Folder M890)
    - "Female Patriotism," undated, (engraving) (Box 22, Folder M891)
    - Fendall, Philip Ricard (1794-1868), undated, (black-and-white photograph) (Folder M892)
    - Ferrero, Edward, undated, (engraving) (Folder M893)
    - Few, Mary Reamy (Thomas), undated, (black-and-white photograph) (Folder M894)
    - Few, Rachel (Kendrick), undated, (card photograph) (Folder M895)
    - Few, William, 1888, 1800s and undated, (3 engravings and 1 card photograph) (Folder M896)
      Negatives available.
      One engraving from Georgia Hist. Society.
      One photograph removed to Oversize Subseries, Box M03, Folder OV79. Includes Few's signature.
    - Fillmore, Millard, 1800s, (engraving) (Folder M897)
    - Fillmore, Millard, 1800s, (engraving) (Folder M898)
    - Finley, The Rev. James B., undated, (engraving) (Folder M899)
    - Fitzclarence, George Augustus Frederick, First Earl of Munster, undated, (engraving) (Folder M900)
    - Fitzroy, Lady Charles, undated, (engraving) (Folder M901)
    - Fitzwilliam, William Wentworth, Fourth Earl Fitzwilliam, 1835, (engraving) (Folder M902)
    - Flowers, George Washington, undated, (card photograph) (Folder M903)
    - Flowers, George Washington, undated, (black-and-white photograph) (Folder M904)
    - Flowers, William Washington, undated, (black-and-white photograph)
      Removed to Oversized Series, Box M03 Folder OV80.
    - Foote, A. H., 1862, 1865 and 1800s, (3 engravings) (Folder M905)
    - Forbes, Duncan (1685-1747), undated, (engraving) (Folder M906)
    - Forbes, Sir William (1739-1806), undated, (engraving) (Folder M907)
    - Forbes, William A. (1846-1919), undated, (card photograph) (Folder M908)
      Gift of Harry L. Mintz, Hallsboro, N.C. -- photograph from an album purchased from the McKenzie Estate, Whiteville, N.C.
    - Ford, Henry, Jacob Herbert, and "Fellow," 1928, (black-and-white photograph) (Folder M909)
      Transferred from the Parapsychology Laboratory papers.
    - "Forjadores de Imperio," [Forgers of Empire], 1900s, (12 postcards) (Folder M910.1)
      From a set of 30 postcards.
    - "Forjadores de Imperio," [Forgers of Empire], 1900s, (12 postcards) (Folder M910.2)
    - "Forjadores de Imperio," [Forgers of Empire], 1900s, (6 postcards) (Folder M910.3)
    - Forrest, Nathan Bedford, 1800s, (3 engravings and 1 clipping) (Folder M911)
      Clipping is a reproduction of a full length sketch.
    - Foster, John Gray, 1800s, (engraving) (Folder M912)
    - Fothergill, John, undated, (engraving) (Folder M913)
    - Founding Fathers, "Laying the Foundation of World Leadership," undated, (color illustration)
      Reproduction of an oil painting.
      Removed to Oversize Subseries, Box M04, Folder OV81.
    - Fourier, Charles, undated, (card photograph) (Folder M914)
    - Fox, Charles James (1749-1806), 1835 and 1800s, (4 engravings) (Folder M915)
    - Fox, Henry Richard Vassall, Third Baron Holland, undated, (engraving) (Folder M916)
    - Fox, John William Jr., undated, (black-and-white photograph) (Folder M917)
    - Franklin, Benjamin, 1818, 1906, and 1900s, (1 engraving, 1 color illustration, and 1 clipping) (Folder M918)
      Transferred from the Marmaduke Floyd Collection. See also M1791 in the People Series for an additional engraving.
    - Franklin, Benjamin, undated, (4 engravings) (Folder M919)
      One image has a negative available. See also M1791 in the People Series for an additional engraving.
    - Franklin, William Buel, undated, (2 engravings) (Folder M920)
    - Fraser, Rev. F. L., undated, (card photograph) (Folder M921)
    - Fraser, Simon, Twelfth Baron Lovat, undated, (engraving) (Folder M922)
    - Frederick II (Frederick the Great), King of Prussia, undated, (engraving) (Folder M923)
    - Frederick II (Frederick the Great), King of Prussia, 1878, (color illustration)
      Removed to Oversize Subseries, Box M04, Folder OV82.
    - Frederick III, Emperor of Germany and King of Prussia (1888), 1878, (card photograph) (Folder M924)
      "This photograph was taken when Frederick was Crown Prince and temporary Regent while his father William I recovered from an assassination attempt."
    - Frederick Augustus, Duke of York and Albany, undated, (black-and-white illustration) (Folder M925)
      Reproduction of a full-length portrait in pencil.
    - Freeling, Sir Francis, undated, (engraving) (Folder M926)
    - Fremantle, Sir Arthur James Lyon, undated, (black-and-white photograph) (Folder M927)
    - Fremont, John C., 1862 and 1800s, (3 engravings) (Folder M928)
    - French noblewomen, [12 portraits], undated, (engraving)
      This image contains 12 separate portraits on one sheet.
      Removed to Oversize Subseries, Box M04, Folder OV83.
    - Frost, Robert, undated, (black-and-white photograph) (Folder M928a)
    - Fuller, Edwin Wiley, undated, (1 black-and-white illustration and 1 black-and-white photograph) (Folder M929)
      Both images are reproductions of the same charcoal drawing.
    - Fuller, Sarah Margaret, undated, (engraving) (Folder M930)
    - Fulton, Robert, undated, (2 engravings) (Folder M931)
    - Fuseli, Henry (Johann Heinrich Fuessli), 1834, (engraving) (Folder M932)
    - Gaffney, Commander John Jerome, 1900s, (black-and-white photograph) (Folder M933)
      Inscribed to Admiral Samuel McGowan.
    - Gaines, Edmund Pendleton, undated, (engraving) (Folder M934)
    - Gaines, Francis Pendleton, undated, (black-and-white photograph) (Folder M935)
    - Galbraith, John Kenneth, 1900s, (black-and-white photographic illustration) (Folder M936)
      Photograph comes from a book jacket.
    - Gales, Weston Raleigh, undated, (black-and-white photographic illustration) (Folder M937)
    - Galileo [Galilei, Galileo], undated, (engraving) (Folder M938)
    - Gallatin, Robert, undated, (engraving) (Folder M939)
    - Galt, Laura Talbot, undated, (card photograph) (Folder M940)
    - Gannaway, William T., undated, (1 black-and-white photograph, 1 black-and-white photographic illustration, and 1 card photograph) (Folder M941)
    - Garden, Alexander, II (1757-1829), undated, (card photograph) (Folder M942)
    - Garfield, James Abram, 1800s, (engraving) (Folder M943)
    - Garner, John Nance, undated, (black-and-white photograph) (Folder M944)
    - Garnett, Richard Brooke, undated, (card photograph) (Folder M945)
    - Garrettson, Rev. Freeborn, undated, (engraving) (Folder M946)
    - Garrison, William Lloyd, 1834 Apr. 8, (engraving) (Folder M947)
    - Gaston, William (Van Noppen - pub.), undated, (2 engravings) (Folder M948)
    - Gastrell, Lucius J., 1870, (engraving) (Folder M949)
    - George I, King of Great Britain, 1700s, (engraving) (Folder M950)
      Removed to Oversize Subseries, Box LG03, Folder OV84.
    - George II, King of Great Britain, 1700s, (2 engravings) (Folder M951)
      One item removed to Oversize Subseries, Box M04, Folder OV85.
    - George III, King of Great Britain, 1759 July, (engraving) (Folder M952)
      From The New Royal and Universal Magazine, or Gentleman and Lady's Companion.
    - George III, King of Great Britain, 1805-1820 and 1800s, (6 engravings) (Folder M953)
      Three items removed to Oversize Series, Box M04, Folder OV86.
    - George IV, King of Great Britain, 1818 and 1800s, (2 engravings and 1 black-and-white illustration) (Folder M954)
      Illustration is a reproduction of an engraving.
    - George V, King, 1919, (postcard) (Folder M955)
    - George, Walter Franklin, 1956, (black-and-white photograph) (Folder M956)
    - Germaine, Lord George, undated, (engraving) (Folder M957)
    - Gevartius, Jan Gaspar (1593-1666), undated, (engraving) (Folder M958)
      Professor at Louvain University. Born in Antwerp.
    - Gibbs, J. Willard, undated, (card photograph) (Folder M959)
    - Giles, Mary, undated, (black-and-white photograph) (Folder M960)
    - Giles, Persis, undated, (card photograph) (Box 23, Folder M961)
    - Giles, Sue, undated, (card photograph) (Folder M962)
    - Giles, Theresa, undated, (2 card photographs) (Folder M963)
      Negatives available of larger image.
    - Gillmore, Quincy Adams, 1800s, (2 engravings) (Folder M964)
    - Gilmer, George Rockingham, undated, (engraving) (Folder M965)
    - Girl Scouts of America in Savannah, Ga., 1915 and circa 1910s, (7 black-and-white photographs) (Folder M966.1)
    - Girl Scouts of America in Savannah, Ga., 1915 and 1910, (5 black-and-white photographs) (Folder M966.2)
      One photograph has negatives available.
    - Gladstone, Herbert John, First Viscount Gladstone, undated, (postcard) (Folder M967)
    - Gladstone, William Ewert, 1800s, (2 engravings) (Folder M968)
    - Glasgow, Ellen, 1973 Oct. 19, (handbill) (Folder M969)
    - Glenn, Edwin Forbes, 1889-1907 and 1900s, (5 black-and-white photographs) (Folder M970.1)
      Contains an itemized list with descriptions of the photographs in folders M970.1-970.3.
    - Glenn, Edwin Forbes, 1916-1918 and 1900s, (6 black-and-white photographs) (Folder M970.2)
    - Glenn, Edwin Forbes, 1918 and 1900s, (5 black-and-white photographs) (Folder M970.3)
    - Godwin, Mary (Wollstonecraft), undated, (engraving) (Folder M971)
    - Goldsborough, William W., undated, (lithograph)
      Removed to Oversize Subseries, Box M04, Folder OV87.
    - Gonzales, William Elliott, 1900s, (black-and-white photograph)
      Removed to Oversize Subseries, Box M04, Folder OV88.
    - Gordon, Duchess of, 1806, (engraving) (Folder M972)
    - Gordon, George Hamilton, Fourth Earl of Aberdeen, 1840, (engraving) (Folder M973)
    - Gordon, James Byron, 1800s, (card photograph) (Folder M974)
    - Gordon, John Brown, 1900s, (1 color illustration, 1 engraving, and 3 black-and-white photographs) (Folder M975)
      Two of the photographs are reproductions of engravings.
    - Gordon, William Washington, 1800s, (black-and-white photograph) (Folder M976)
    - Gough, Hugh, First Viscount Gough, undated, (engraving)
      Removed to Oversize Subseries, Box M04, Folder OV89 (no folder created in Main Collection).
    - Grafigni, Madame de, 1806, (engraving) (Folder M977)
      French novelist and associate of Voltaire.
    - Graham, Thomas, Baron Lynedoch, 1831 and 1800s, (4 engravings) (Folder M978)
    - Granger, Gordon, undated, (engraving) (Folder M979)
    - Grant, Ulysses Simpson, 1885 June 19, (card photograph) (Folder M980)
    - Grant, Ulysses Simpson, 1800s, (2 engravings and 2 black-and-white illustrations) (Folder M981.1)
      Two items removed to Box M04, Folder OV90 in the Oversize Subseries.
    - Grant, Ulysses Simpson, 1800s, (3 engravings) (Folder M981.2)
    - Grant, William (1752-1832), 1833, (engraving) (Folder M982)
    - Gray, George, undated, (black-and-white photographic illustration) (Folder M983)
    - Gray, James A., undated, (1 black-and-white photograph and 1 black-and-white photographic illustration) (Folder M984)
    - Greeley, Horace, 1800s, (engraving) (Folder M985)
    - Green, George Sears, 1800s, (engraving) (Folder M986)
    - Green, John R., undated, (engraving) (Folder M987)
    - Green, Wharton Jackson, 1868 June, (card photograph) (Folder M988)
      Transferred from the C. C. Clay papers.
    - Greene, Nathanael, 1785 Aug. 12, 1872, 1700s and 1800s, (7 engravings) (Folder M989.1)
    - Greene, Nathanael, 1700s and 1800s, (5 engravings and 1 sketch) (Folder M989.2)
    - Grenville, Thomas, 1835 and 1847, (2 engravings) (Folder M990)
    - Grenville, William Wyndham, Baron Grenville, 1832, (engraving) (Folder M991)
    - Gresham, Sir Thomas, 1813 Jan. 1, (engraving) (Folder M992)
    - Griffin, W. Hunter, undated, (lithograph) (Folder M993)
    - Griffith, Thomas W., undated, (lithograph) (Folder M994)
      Image is a silhouette.
    - Grime, Jo, 1867 Aug., (card photograph) (Folder M995)
      Image is a reproduction of a pen and ink sketch by Judge W. B. Rudman.
    - Grissom, Eugene, undated, (card photograph) (Folder M996)
    - Griswold, Alexander Veits, undated, (engraving) (Folder M997)
    - Grose, Francis (circa 1731-1791), 1700s, (engraving) (Folder M998)
    - Grotius (De Groot), Hugo, undated, (engraving) (Folder M999)
    - Grundy, Felix, undated, (engraving) (Folder M1000)
    - Guest, Romeo Holland, 1900s, (black-and-white photograph) (Folder M1001)
    - Gustavus II or Gustavus Adolphus, King of Sweden (1611-1632), undated, (engraving) (Folder M1002)
    - Gustavus Adolphus IV, King of Sweden, 1808 June 1, (engraving) (Folder M1003)
    - Gwinnett, Button, undated, (black-and-white photograph) (Folder M1004)
      "A reproduction of a spurious portrait."
    - Gwinnett, Button, undated, (4 black-and-white photographs) (Folder M1005)
      Photographs are reproductions of a painting.
    - Habersham, James, undated, (2 engravings) (Folder M1006)
    - Habersham, John, undated, (2 engravings) (Folder M1007)
    - Habersham, Joseph, undated, (2 engravings) (Folder M1008)
    - Hackney, Edward Carney, 1800s, (card photograph) (Folder M1009)
    - Halder, Oberst Franz, 1953, (3 black-and-white photographs) (Folder M1010)
    - Hale, Everett Edward, 1900s, (clipping) (Folder M1011)
    - Hales, Stephen and Robert Herrick, 1799 Jan., (engraving) (Folder M1012)
      Image contains an engraving of each man on a single page.
    - Hall, Granville Stanley, 1800s, (card photograph) (Folder M1013)
    - Hall, Lyman, 1871, 1868 and 1800s, (2 black-and-white photographs and 2 engravings) (Folder M1014)
      Photographs are reproductions of engravings.
    - Halleck, Henry Wager (1815-1872), 1862, (engraving) (Folder M1015)
    - Hamilton, Alexander, undated, (engraving) (Folder M1016)
      See also M1792 in the People Series for an additional engraving.
    - Hamilton, James, Second Earl of Arran and Duke of Chatelherault, undated, (engraving) (Folder M1017)
    - Hamilton, James, Second Marquis of Hamilton, undated, (engraving) (Folder M1018)
    - Hamilton, Marmaduke, 1800s, (card photograph) (Box 24, Folder M1019)
    - Hamilton, William Baskerville, 1969, (2 black-and-white photographs) (Folder M1020)
    - Hampton, Wade, 1800s, (2 engravings and 2 black-and-white photographic illustrations) (Folder M1021)
      The illustrations are from Charles E. Jones' Scrapbook.
    - Hancock, John, undated, (engraving) (Folder M1022)
    - Hancock, Winfield Scott, 1800s, (2 engravings) (Folder M1023)
    - Hanes, John Wesley, undated, (engraving) (Folder M1024)
    - Hanes, Pleasant Henderson, undated, (engraving)
      Removed to Oversize Subseries, Box M04, Folder OV91.
    - Hanly, J. Frank, 1900s, (black-and-white photographic illustration) (Folder M1025)
    - Hardee, William Joseph, 1800s, (3 engravings) (Folder M1026)
    - Harden, William, 1800s, (card photograph) (Folder M1027)
    - Hardie, James Allen, 1800s, (card photograph) (Folder M1028)
    - Hardwicke, Philip Yorke, Earl of, undated, (engraving) (Folder M1029)
    - Hardy, Sir Thomas Masterman, First Baronet, 1834, (engraving) (Folder M1030)
    - Harlan, John M., undated, (engraving) (Folder M1031)
    - Harris, Joel Chandler, 1910, (postcard) (Folder M1032)
    - Harrison, Benjamin (1833-1901), 1800s, (engraving) (Folder M1033)
    - Harrison, George P., Jr., undated, (engraving) (Folder M1034)
      Includes possibly authentic signature of George P. Harrison Jr.
    - Harrison, Henry Sydnor, undated, (black-and-white photograph) (Folder M1035)
      Transferred from the Henry S. Harrison Papers.
    - Harrison, William Henry, 1861 and 1800s, (3 engravings) (Folder M1036)
      One engraving removed to Box LG03, folder OV92 in the Oversize Subseries.
    - Hawke, Edward, First Baron Hawke (1705-1781), 1834 Sept. 1, (engraving)
      Removed to Oversize Subseries, Box M04, Folder OV93.
    - Hawley, Joseph Roswell, 1800s, (1 engraving and 1 card photograph) (Folder M1037)
    - Hayden, Hiram, 1961, (black-and-white photograph) (Folder M1038)
    - Hayes, Rutherford Birchard, 1800s, (engraving) (Folder M1039)
    - Hayne, Paul Hamilton, 1800s, (1 card photograph and 1 engraving) (Folder M1040)
    - Hayne, Paul Hamilton, 1888, (black-and-white photograph)
      Includes faint signature.
      Removed to Oversize Subseries, Box M04, Folder OV94.
    - Hayne, Robert Young, undated, ( engraving and one (black-and-white illustration) (Folder M1041)
      Illustration removed to Box M04, Folder OV95 in the Oversize Subseries.
    - Haywood, Will H., Jr., undated, (engraving) (Folder M1042)
    - Hazen, William Babcock, undated, (engraving) (Folder M1043)
    - Hazlitt, Henry, 1900s, (black-and-white photograph) (Folder M1044)
    - Heintzelman, Samuel Peter, 1800s, (engraving) (Folder M1045)